（海崎(かいざき)）ああ…
How many did you fail?
（大神(おおが)）赤点 いくつ？
Seven. Will I have to
take make-ups again?
（海崎）７… また再試かな
After failing that many, you must be
crazy to hope for no make-ups.
それだけ 取っといて
再試じゃないかもとか—
頭おかしいでしょ
（小野屋(おのや)）ウフッ
How'd you do, An-chan?
杏(あん)ちゃんは どうだったの？
Seems like you did okay?
なかなか よさそうな感じだけど
I passed everything this time!
今回は 赤点なし
Whoa! Awesome!
えっ すっげえ
Hard to believe you got a two
on math last time!
前回 数学２点だったとは
思えない進歩！
エヘヘ… ごめんね 私だけ 新太(あらた)君
Sorry I passed without you, Arata-kun.
ん… 裏切り者
You traitor...
（小野屋･大神）イエイ！
If you failed more than three,
you get make-ups.
（天津(あまつ)）
赤点３つ以上の人は 再試だからね
If that's you, come see me after school.
該当者は
放課後 先生のところに来るように
Have fun!
（小野屋･大神）
いってらっしゃい
〜♪
Rift
Staff Room
（天津）ハア…
Are you okay, Kaizaki-kun?
海崎君 大丈夫？
That isn't the word I'd use.
（海崎）
あまり大丈夫じゃない… ですよね
At all.
Class 3-3 Roll no.4 Kaizaki Arata
1st Mid-Term Report Card
Were you sick or something?
（天津）体調でも悪かったとか？
Nope. That's how I did
in the pink of health.
（海崎）いいえ 万全で それです
Were you entering answers
in the wrong fields?
回答欄 ずれて書いちゃったとか？
Did you study the wrong things?
勉強する範囲を間違えてたとか？
（海崎）
先生 現実を受け止めてください
Sensei, please face reality.
I made no mistakes, and this is the result.
何のミスもなく それです
ハア
I'm sorry.
（海崎）すみません
Well, last time you didn't give up
and took the make-ups until you passed.
まあ 前回の再試も—
途中で投げ出さずに
合格まで やり遂げたし
So I think you'll be fine.
海崎君なら大丈夫だって思ってる
Hang in there!
頑張って
そうだ
Yeah...
I could have gotten sick of it,
given up, and run away.
あきらめて 嫌になって
逃げ出す道もあったのに
Maybe... I am starting to change.
俺 少しは変われてるんだろうか
まあ
１人だったら 逃げ出してたかもな
Though I might have run
if I'd been alone.
（玉来(たまらい)）失礼します
Excuse me!
（天津）来たわね ほのか
There you are, Honoka.
Here I am...
（玉来）来ました エヘヘ…
Kaizaki-kun, this is our captain.
海崎君 これ うちのキャプテン
ああ 先生
バレー部の顧問だったんですね
Oh, you're the coach of the volleyball team?
（天津）うん
（玉来）どうも 海崎君
Yeah.
Hey there, Kaizaki-kun.
I hear you're always
helping Rena out.
玲奈(れな)が いつもお世話になってます
ええっ！ いや こちらこそ
No, she's the one helping me.
So, you failed five, Honoka?
（天津）
ええと… ほのかは赤点５つね
Gimme a break here.
もう 勘弁してよ！
エヘヘ… ごめんなさい
Sorry.
（天津）キャプテンが
再試で試合に来れませんなんて—
If the captain's too busy taking make-ups
to play, it'll set a bad example!
示しがつかないんだから
Make sure you pass these next week!
１週間で ちゃんと合格すること
え 頑張ります
Uh, I'll try!
Oh, she's the same as me?
（海崎）
何と 仲間だったか！
The tournament in June is the
last time you third-years will play.
６月の大会—
あんたたち３年生にとっちゃ
最後の試合でしょ？
Without you, we might well
get eliminated in round one!
ほのかが いないと—
初戦敗退ってことも
ありえるんだから
Please, do your best to pass.
ほんと 頑張ってよ
Don't worry. It's a team sport.
大丈夫ですよ
団体競技なんですから—
Even if I'm not there, they'll—
私がいなくても
ちゃんと みんなが…
（天津）ほのか！
（玉来）あっ
Honoka!
Trusting your teammates is good.
仲間を頼るのは いいことだよ
But they can't replace you.
でも ほのかの代わりは いないの
Maybe that puts pressure on you,
プレッシャーかもしれないけど
それだけの力があるし—
but you're just that good,
and we all know it.
みんなが認めてる
Have more confidence.
もっと気を強く持って
Don't be so willing to hand over
your spot to someone else.
自分の場所を誰かに譲ろうだなんて
簡単にしないで
Okay.
はい
Goodbye.
（海崎）失礼しました
（玉来）失礼しました
Goodbye.
Troubled, Amatsu-sensei?
（宇佐(うさ)）お悩みですな 天津先生
As good as she is,
she just lacks appetite.
あれだけの実力を持ちながら—
どうにも
欲というか 自信がないんですよ
Or maybe confidence?
Power that's too great
destroys its surroundings.
（宇佐）大きすぎる力は
周りを滅ぼすからな
Huh?
（天津）え？
（宇佐）いや 何にせよ—
Anyway, I wish the boys' volleyball team
had that kind of problem.
わが男子バレー部にとっては
うらやましい悩みだなと…
Yeah, you guys suck.
そうですね 弱小ですもんね
I hope you at least make it
past the first round this year.
今年は
初戦くらい突破できるといいですね
（宇佐）
アイツらの悪口はやめろ！
Don't badmouth them!
They're doing the best they can!
アイツらだって
頑張ってんだよ！
Tamarai-san, you didn't have to
take make-ups last time, right?
（海崎）玉来さん
前回は再試じゃなかったよね？
前回は３教科だけだったから
There were only three subjects last time.
But the mid-terms and finals have so many...
中間とか期末とか 教科が多いと…
（海崎）そっか
Ah, I see...
I'm here on a sports scholarship.
私 スポーツ推薦で
青葉(あおば)に入ったんだ
だから 勉強のほうは ちょっと苦手
So I'm not the best at studying.
スポーツ推薦だったら
その辺 優遇されないの？
Don't they cut scholarship athletes
a little slack on that?
Exempt you from make-ups,
or something?
再試は免除とか
（玉来）ないよ
Nope.
もともと
そんなに部活に力入れてないし—
It's a prep school.
Sports aren't really a big thing here.
進学校だしね
Then why choose Aoba?
じゃあ 何で青葉に？
Couldn't you have gone to
a school with a better team?
もっと 強豪校とかに
入る道もあったん… じゃ…
Sorry. None of my business, huh?
ごめん
急に いろいろ聞いちゃったね
N-Nah, it's okay.
あっ ううん 大丈夫
Sorry, I just spaced out.
ごめん ぼーっとしちゃってて
I picked Aoba because Aki-chan
and Nobu-chan were going here,
青葉を選んだのは—
アキちゃんと ノブちゃんが
ここに行くって言ってたから—
and I thought, "I'll go with them!"
じゃあ 私もみたいな感じで…
Aki-chan? Nobu-chan?
アキちゃん ノブちゃん？
あっ 犬飼(いぬかい)くんと朝地(あさじ)くん
Oh, Inukai-kun and Asaji-kun.
ああ 幼なじみの？
Oh, your childhood friends?
Huh? Oh, wow!
えっ すごい
私 海崎君と話すの初めてなのに
詳しい！
I've never talked to you before.
I'm surprised you knew.
（海崎）
狩生(かりう)や大神から よく話 聞くからな
Kariu and Oga talk about you a lot.
You and Kariu are pretty close?
仲いいよね 狩生と
Yeah!
Thanks to Rena, high school volleyball
has been super fun!
玲奈のおかげで
高校の部活は 本当に楽しかった！
感謝しても しきれないくらい
I can't thank her enough!
あっ 私 このまま部活行くね
Oh, I'm headed to practice now.
Okay.
そう言えば
海崎君に聞きたいこと あったんだ
Oh, right. There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
小野屋さんって 大神君のことが
好きだったりするのかな？
Does Onoya-san have, like,
a crush on Oga-kun or what?
Pretty sure she doesn't.
ないと思うよ
Really?
（玉来）ほんと？
（海崎）うん ない
Yep. I'm sure.
Ah, youth...
（海崎）青春だな
Hishiro-san. You're still here?
日代(ひしろ)さん まだ学校いたんだ
海崎さん
また 呼び出されてたんですか？
Kaizaki-san...
Were you called to the staff room again?
So how have you been?
そっちはどう 最近？
How... you ask?
（日代）どうとは？
You've been eating lunch
with Kariu and Tamarai-san.
（海崎）狩生と玉来さんと
お昼食べてるみたいだけど
すごいじゃん
どんどん友達増えてんじゃん
That's great.
You're making more friends.
はい おかげさまで
Yes.
Thanks to you.
Ah! She looks happy.
（海崎）あっ うれしそう
Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
are both really nice,
狩生さんと玉来さん—
お２人とも
とてもいい子で 仲がよくて—
and get along so well,
it kinda makes me jealous.
見てて うらやましくなるぐらい
（海崎）日代さん？
Hishiro-san?
Sorry. My consciousness left me.
すみません 意識が飛んでました
That sounds bad.
（海崎）大丈夫か それ？
You seem like you've gotten used to school
and are enjoying yourself.
（日代）海崎さんこそ—
もう学校にも慣れて
毎日 楽しそうで
（海崎）え そうか？
Do I?
毎日 必死だよ
I'm barely hanging on.
再試 含めて
ずっとテスト受けてるしね
With all these make-ups,
I've done nothing but take tests.
（日代）そう言えば…
（海崎）ん？
Oh, that's right.
Um... uh...
（日代）あの… あれ…
She's always with you...
the four-eyed braid girl...
いつも一緒にいる
眼鏡の 三つ編みの…
（海崎）ああ 杏？
Oh, An?
それです 杏さん
That's right, An-san.
Does An-san...
杏さんって—
...have a crush on Kazu-kun?
カズ君のこと
好きだったりするんでしょうか？
Huh?
ブッハハハ…
それは ないと思うよ
I don't think she does.
（日代）そうですか
Is that so?
See, Kariu?
（海崎）何だよ 狩生
運動では 玉来さんに—
You can't beat Tamarai-san at sports
or Hishiro-san at studying,
勉強では日代さんに勝てないと—
so you drove yourself into a corner,
あんなに
自分を追い詰めてたけど—
but they both love you.
２人ともから
すげえ愛されてんじゃん
（海崎）日代さん もう帰る？
（日代）はい
Headed home, Hishiro-san?
Yes.
Wanna walk with me to the station?
駅まで一緒に帰ろうか
はい 喜んで
Yes, sir.
アハハ… 居酒屋かよ
Am I your captain now?
Aye-aye, sir!
はい 喜んで！
Why'd you suddenly yell?
何でテンション寄せてきたの？
（日代）
フリというやつかなと思いまして
I thought you wanted me to.
Stop it! The deadpan jokes are killing me!
やめて 唐突に真顔でボケるの
（日代）すみません…
Sorry.
Kariu-senpai.
（部員）狩生先輩
We don't need to put the net away, right?
今日も ネット
片づけなくていいんですか？
Yeah, I'll still be using it.
（狩生）
ああ 使うから そのままでいいよ
ほのか どうする？ 居残り練
Honoka, are you staying for more?
ああ… 今日は やめとく
帰って勉強しなきゃ
Not today.
I've gotta get home and study.
Yeah.
だね
（玉来）あっ そうだ 玲奈
（狩生）ん？
Oh. That's right, Rena!
Apparently Onoya-san doesn't
have a crush on Oga-kun.
（玉来）小野屋さんは—
大神君のことが
好きってわけじゃないってさ
Huh?!
エヘヘ… 海崎君に聞いちゃった
I asked Kaizaki-kun.
（狩生）
何 あのバカに勝手なことを！
What? You asked that idiot?!
私は別に…
I never...!
There, there.
See ya!
じゃあね
Idiot.
バカ…
She should be focused
on her studying, not me.
人のことより
自分の勉強のこと 心配しなさいよ
..the last time you third-years will play.
あんたたち３年生にとっちゃ
最後の試合でしょ？
This team can only play together
for three more weeks.
（玉来）今のメンバーで
バレーができるのも 残り３週間
I've gotta pass those make-ups fast!
再試なんて
さっさと合格しなくちゃね
うわ 部室に傘あったかな
Was there an umbrella in the clubroom?
（部員）今日さ
玉来先輩 来るの遅くなかった？
Wasn't Tamarai-senpai late today?
（部員）ああ
テストのたびに再試になってて—
Oh, apparently she ends up having to take
make-ups every time there are tests.
いつものことらしいよ
（部員）えっ… いいの それ？
And that's okay?
（部員）
まあ あれだけ うまかったら—
As good as she is, she probably
doesn't need to practice.
練習なんて
しなくていいんじゃない？
You can say that again!
（部員）確かに言えてる
（部員）フフ…
Maybe.
（部員）かもね フフッ
Stop trying so hard!
（女子生徒）
それ以上 頑張らないでよ！
差が どんどん開きすぎて
こっちが やる気なくす
You keep getting better, and I can't—
（女子生徒）何で部員じゃない
あんたが大会に出るの？
Whatever! You're still going
to the tournament!
（女子生徒）
いいよね 才能ある人は
Must be nice to have talent.
Must be nice.
（部員）いいよね ほんと
普通 それだけ赤点あったら—
Most people wouldn't be allowed to play
if they kept failing like that.
大会とか
出させてもらえないんじゃない？
それでも
キャプテンでレギュラーとかさ…
But she's a starter and the captain.
（部員）
しょうがないよ 実力あるんだし
Well, she's just that good.
I bet it pisses Kariu-senpai off.
（部員）狩生先輩とか
絶対よく思ってないと思う
（部員）だよね！
Yeah, for sure!
（部員）才能あるからってさ
Just 'cause she's talented.
（部員）狩生先輩…
Kariu-senpai...
Rena?
玲奈？
Honoka practices after you all go home,
every single day.
（狩生）みんなが帰ったあとも
毎日 練習してるわよ ほのかは
She loves volleyball more than anything.
バレーが好きでしかたないって顔で
毎日毎日
勉強のほうだって—
She has trouble keeping her grades up,
ついていくのも大変なはずなのに
必死で頑張ってる
but she works her ass off at that, too.
Yeah, her raw talent is amazing,
and I'm jealous.
確かに 悔しいくらい—
もともとのセンスが
ずばぬけてるけど—
それだけじゃない
努力の人だって思うから—
But because I know that's not all she is,
and because I know the work
she puts in, I respect her.
心から尊敬してるし—
And that's why I work so hard.
おかげで私も頑張れる
Before you start bitching,
maybe try harder than her?
グチグチと文句言ってる暇が
あるなら—
まず ほのかよりも頑張ったら？
She's got more talent than you, so why
would you let her beat you in effort?
実力で負けてるのに
努力でも負けてて どうするの!?
Excuse me!
（部員）失礼しました！
（部員）すみません！
Sorry!
（部員）お… お疲れさまでした！
Bye!
H-Hey!
（狩生）あっ コラ！
何で そこで—
Why wouldn't that make them
stay for more practice?
居残り練つきあいますとかに
ならないのよ
Hard to get fired up all alone...
１人だと張り合いないな
Thanks to Rena, high school volleyball
has been super fun!
（玉来）玲奈のおかげで
高校の部活は 本当に楽しかった！
Thank you, Rena.
（玉来）
ありがとう 玲奈
Hey there, Tama-chan.
（すみれ）
いらっしゃい タマちゃん
Ah, Sumire-chan!
あっ すみれちゃん
お邪魔してます
Thanks for having me.
再試に備えて 勉強会？
Studying for make-ups?
Good, good.
感心 感心
I wanna get them over with
so I can focus on practice.
早く再試なんか終わらせて
部活に集中したいから
We can't play together much longer.
みんなと一緒にやれるのも
あと少しなんだし
ウフッ
Well, if he's useful,
こんなのでも役に立つなら
いくらでも使っちゃっていいからね
（犬飼(いぬかい)）ちょ…
何すんだ やめろ！
use him all you like!
What are you doing? Stop that!
Okay. Good luck!
じゃ 頑張ってね
（玉来）はい
Right!
Should I call Nobu?
（犬飼）ノブ 呼ぼうか
（玉来）えっ…
He's better then me at—
アイツのほうが 俺より…
（玉来）いいよ いいよ
No, don't.
You're more at my level,
which is perfect.
アキちゃん程度のほうが
話が通じて ちょうどいいんだよ
Am I?
（犬飼）程度？
（玉来）それに ノブちゃん
もう寝てるかなって思って
And I figure Nobu-chan
will be in bed already.
（朝地）ふ スヤ…
Zzz...
確かに ジジイみたいだからな
あいつ
Yeah, he's like an old man.
The tournament is on
June 15th and 16th, right?
（犬飼）
６月の15と16だっけ 大会？
Yup.
見に行くよ ノブと一緒に
I'll be there.
Nobu, too.
Huh? But we're not a strong team,
not like in junior high.
えっ でも—
うち 中学の時みたいな
強いチームじゃないよ
I know.
知ってる
That's not why I wanna go.
別に 強いチームだから
見たいんじゃない
むしろ 中学の時は
あまり見る気にならなかった
Honestly, I couldn't be bothered
to watch in junior high.
But now...
（犬飼）でも 今は—
タマが楽しそうだから
...you're having fun.
You seem so alive playing with them.
そんなチームなら—
タマが生き生きとプレーしてるとこ
見てみたいって ノブも言ってた
Nobu and I both wanna see that.
We'll be there.
見に行くよ
Okay!
I'll play my best!
頑張るからね！
Cool.
But first, make-ups.
でも その前に再試な
（玉来）はい…
Right.
Hello.
Congratulations on your make-ups!
（夜明(よあけ)）
再試 おめでとうございます
It ain't a good thing!
めでたくねえよ！
（夜明）えっ でも—
Oh? But because you got
summoned to the staff room,
赤点で呼び出されたおかげで
日代さんと帰りの時間が合って—
you could leave at
the same time as Hishiro-san
放課後デートが
できちゃったわけですし
and have an after-school date!
駅まで一緒に歩いただけですう！
We just walked to the station together!
What's your plan this time?
どうするんです 今回は？
Huh? I haven't got any plan.
どうするも何も—
また大神に教えてもらいながら
何とか
I'll just have to push through it
with Oga's help.
I was trying to study on my own just now.
今も自分なりに勉強してたとこだよ
Well, well. Keep up the—
それはそれは 頑張ってください…
困ったら 私もいますからね！
If you're in trouble, remember I'm here!
Ask me anytime!
頼ってくださいね
（海崎）杏… 杏と一緒にいるのか
夜明さん？
An?
Is An with you, Yoake-san?
まあ 会社ですので
Yes... we're at work.
席が隣なんですよ
I sit next to him!
うるさいな 入ってくるな！
Shut up and go away.
では 海崎さん また明日
Okay, Kaizaki-san, see you tomorrow!
Huh? I still wanna talk—
（小野屋）え まだ話したいです
（夜明）ん… くっ…
（夜明）失礼します！
Goodbye now!
（小野屋）ああ ちょ ちょ…
（夜明）おいっ！
Ah, wait, wait... ah!
（携帯電話の操作音）
（海崎）ふん…
What the... do they like each other, or not?
何なんだ？
仲がいいんだか悪いんだか…
フッ… 結局 何の用だったんだよ
What did he call about, anyway?
ハア さあ
Okay.
Let's do this.
頑張りますか
Mid-term Make-ups
採点 終わったわよ
I've finished grading your tests.
Tamarai-san.
玉来さん
You passed.
合格よ
ああ よかった
Thank goodness!
（すみれ）海崎君は—
Kaizaki-kun...
...see you next week.
また来週もね
Yeah...
はーい…
エヘヘ 海崎君 お先に
Bye bye, Kaizaki-kun!
Crap!
（海崎）くそっ
I'm off to practice!
じゃあ 私 部活行くね
また 明日ね
See you tomorrow!
（すみれ）待って タマちゃん
（玉来）あ？
Wait, Tama-chan...
You're awfully pale.
顔色がよくないわ
You've been at our place
every night this week.
この１週間
夜は ずっと うちに来てたし—
寝不足なんじゃない？
Did you get enough sleep?
ウフフ… 大丈夫だよ すみれちゃん
I'm fine, Sumire-chan.
Don't push yourself.
あまり無理しちゃダメよ
（玉来）はい ありがとう
Okay. Thanks!
Excuse me!
じゃあ 失礼しまーす
"Tama-chan"?
（海崎）
タマちゃん？ すみれちゃん？
"Sumire-chan"?
How'd the make-ups go?
どうだった 再試？
Did you fail?
ダメだった？
Don't look so happy.
（海崎）ウキウキと聞くなよ
I did.
ダメだったけど
（犬飼）おい
Hey.
How'd Tama do?
（朝地）あ… あ ああ…
（犬飼）タマは どうなった？
た… 玉来さん？
T-Tamarai-san?
合格して 部活行ったよ
She passed and went to practice.
（朝地）う… ああ…
（犬飼）そうか どうも
Okay. Thanks.
（海崎）んっ… 何で
そんな偉そうなんだ？ クソガキ
How can you be so arrogant, you brat?!
Good for Tama-chan!
よかったね タマちゃん
She looked so pale this morning.
朝から顔色悪かったけど
とりあえず一安心
I'm relieved!
Nice spike!
（部員）ナイスキー
ハア…
It's no use. Every hit is weak.
（玉来）
ダメだ 全然 力入んないな
何か 頭も ぼーっとするし
And my mind's not in it, either.
Maybe I should go home early...
今日は
早く帰ったほうが いいかな…
Tamarai-senpai!
（部員）玉来先輩！
（部員）玉来先輩 大丈夫ですか？
Tamarai-senpai! Are you okay?
Sorry...
（玉来）ごめん… 一瞬 目の前が…
Everything went black for a—
I'm okay now.
大丈夫
Kariu-senpai!
（部員）狩生(かりう)先輩！
（部員たち）あ？
Kariu! What's wrong?
（部員）狩生 どうしたの!?
（部員）転がってきたボールを
よけようとして
She tried to avoid a rolling ball, and—
（部員）先生 呼んできて！ 早く！
Call the nurse! Now!
（部員）はいっ
Right!
Rena! Are you okay? Can you stand?
（部員）玲奈 大丈夫？ 立てる？
Rena!
玲奈！
Nurse's Office
It's sprained.
（すみれ）捻挫ね
The bone seems fine,
骨に異常はなさそうだけど
明日 ちゃんと病院に行くこと
but make sure you go
to a hospital tomorrow.
How long to recover?
（天津）どのくらいで治りますか？
Well...
（すみれ）そうね… おそらく—
Most likely two or three weeks.
２〜３週間ってとこかしら
（玉来･狩生）ハッ！
But that's—
そんな！ あっ…
Kariu-san.
狩生さん この時間
おうちの人は誰かいる？
Is there anyone at home right now?
はい
Yes.
Then let's have them come get you.
じゃあ 迎えに来てもらいましょう
I'll go call them.
電話してくるわ
Rena...
玲奈…
Rena.
ごめん…
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize.
（狩生）謝らないでよ
（玉来）あっ
People get injured in practice
all the time.
部活中のケガなんて—
誰でも
起こりうることだし
I tried to avoid the ball
and lost my balance.
ボールを
よけようとして—
バランスを崩したのは
私のミス
That's on me.
でも 私のせいで
玲奈の足元にボールが…
But it was my fault
the ball was even there!
それがなければ…
If I hadn't—
I know that!
（狩生）そうだけど！
（玉来）ハッ…
But you would have dodged it just fine.
（狩生）それでもきっと
ほのかなら うまくよけられた
It's my fault.
私のミスだよ
B-But...
で… でも—
If it's only two weeks,
you'll make the tournament.
２週間なら大会に間に合うよね
早く治るといいね
I hope you get better soon.
It's our last—
（玉来）高校最後の…
（狩生）無理よ
No.
If it's three weeks, I won't make it.
（狩生）
３週間かかったら間に合わないし
Even if it heals in two,
仮に２週間で治ったとしても—
I can't play in a tournament
without practice.
そんな練習休んで
すぐ大会なんて—
I can't.
無理
You can, Rena! You'll make up
for two weeks in no time!
無理じゃないよ！
玲奈なら
２週間ぐらい すぐ取り戻せる
（狩生）無理だっつってんでしょ！
（玉来）ハッ
I said I can't!
I'm no genius!
私は天才じゃないの！
I work and I work,
and I'm barely good enough!
努力して努力して やっとなの！
ほのかには
分からないかもしれないけど
But I guess you wouldn't understand!
If I'm not there,
it won't affect the team at all!
（狩生）私なんかいなくたって
チームには何の影響もないじゃん！
As long as you're there,
we'll win! I don't matter!
ほのか１人いれば
勝てちゃうんだから！
関係ないでしょ！
（狩生）何で…
Why...?
Why?
何で？
（狩生）何で？
Why?
（犬飼）タマ？
（玉来）ハッ
Tama?
What are you doing here?
何してんだよ そんなとこで
部活終わったのか？
Are you done with practice?
そろそろかなって
迎えに行こうとしてたんだよ
We were headed over. We thought
you might be wrapping up.
Tama-chan?
タマちゃん？
アキ！
Aki!
〜♪
NEXT EPISODE
Nobu, you can come with me
to watch Tama play, right?
（犬飼）タマの試合
ノブも一緒に行けるよな？
（朝地）もっちろん！
Of course! We'd better practice!
（朝地）今から練習しとかないとね
（犬飼）えっ…
One, two...
（朝地）せーの！
フレー フレー タマちゃん
"Hooray! Hooray! Tama-chan!"
Come on, Aki.
さあ アキも！
頑張れ 頑張れ タマちゃん
"Do your best, Tama-chan!"
Revenge
聞いてる アキ？
どうした アキ？
You listening to me, Aki?
What's the matter?
（犬飼）空気読め ノブ
Learn to take a hint, Nobu.